<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>On a Wednesday - Articles</title>
		<description></description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feed.articles.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Fran</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well mostly, I have been retired and I'm doing whatever I please today. As I do most every day. I'm going to go up to a friend's. Right now I'm sitting in the park reading my paper. I do that every morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is my backyard. I live two blocks away, over on Waverly and I love living in New York. I love it. I don't know why anybody would want to live anywhere else. Well, that's a little extreme. This is like my backyard. I like coming over here in the morning, I'm too old to enjoy the afternoon and evening nonsense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'd have to say, probably morning. Just because I'm an early person. I didn't like to get up and go to work, but I like to get up in the morning. I was a runner for a long time, and ran in the mornings. When my running was over, the best part of my day was over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's odd, most of my friends that are retired think I'm nuts. &quot;Why don't you sleep late?&quot; Well, sleeping late has never been something I want to do. So yeah, that's the favorite part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gee, I haven't thought that far ahead. I'm going away on Saturday, so I'm taking care of some things for that. I'm going up to Maine for a few days. Some shopping, seeing a friend, nothing very dramatic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:35 a.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/fran/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/fran/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Reuben</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I woke up early, so I'm going to skate for a while, then go to work. And then probably meet up with some friends afterwards, kick back a little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably the morning. I'm an early riser, I just wake up and I'm ready to go. I get out before a lot of my friends do. I get a lot more time skating, which is nice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I have work, so similar to today. Until I get off for a few days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:00 a.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/reuben/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/reuben/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Michelle</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, this morning I am sitting. I am sitting in the sun at the park. It's a perfect morning for it. It's not hot, it's not humid. It's just a lovely way to start the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you do this often?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As much as we can, yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Couple times a week? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It kind of depends. Once it starts getting warm, then it's not a good place for it. What I'll do on some mornings is, where I live it's a corner and the cross breeze is coming from two directions. So I'll just take, well not this chair, but a regular lawn chair and sit by the corner, by the apartment building, get the cross breeze, do that for an hour. Usually I read my newspaper. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;So you're in a bigger apartment building?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;So you can't just sit out on the stoop or anything. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, I don't have a stoop anymore. And I don't have a terrace, I would love a terrace. It's on the list of things I'd love to have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And how long have you lived around here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don't live in the heart of Bay Ridge, I'm sort of on the border. But basically, I've lived here for 45 years. My grandparents lived a block from where I live now. All my life, basically. I actually grew up in Bensonhurst, on 14th avenue, right across the street from the golf course. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And who do you live with now? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My sister. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And what time did you wake up this morning? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;6 o'clock. In the winter I sleep later and go to bed late. Go out when it's warmer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I do like the early morning. I like the quiet of the early morning. When you can open the windows and listen to the birds. And then, again I like late nights. It's quiet. I like the quiet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow it's supposed to rain, and I have a doctors appointment at 3 o'clock. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:00 a.m. on Wednesday, July 31</pubDate>
				<link>/with/michelle/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/michelle/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Juan</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm just getting a morning workout here. Pretty much, just shoot hoops in the morning. That's how I start my day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Every day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, I try to at least. Three times a week, at least. I've been trying to get back in shape, so I figured this would be the best way to start. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you live around here? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I actually live in Staten Island. But I work here and I have a lot of friends here. I usually come to Brooklyn a lot. I'm actually going to meet up with some friends after, so I figured I'd shoot here first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you guys going to do today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today we're going to head over to a friend's house to have a little barbecue. Just have some people over, hang out and enjoy the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up this morning?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I woke up around 6:30. Ate a little something, took a shower then headed out here. I've been here for about 30 minutes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Who do you live with?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now I live with my parents and my brother. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, I don't know if I'll be able to shoot hoops in the morning, but tomorrow I'll be working. So I won't be able to play hoops in the morning. But I'll see if I can get some sort of workout in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And what do you do for work? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work as a clerk in a hospital. I work evening shifts, so I work from 3pm until late at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably the morning. I'm a morning person. I feel like if you have a good start to the day, then the rest of the day should go pretty well. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:15 a.m. on Wednesday, July 31</pubDate>
				<link>/with/juan/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/juan/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Sophie</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well I went to try the bakery, Kayser. It's just around there. It's a French guy and they just started opening a new store and it's really, really good. I got bread and a raspberry financier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Is that all you have planned today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, it's very private. But actually, I took the day off because I'm pregnant and I have a big doctor appointment, so I just didn't want to rush from work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Congratulations! That's really exciting. And what time did you wake up today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like 7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And what is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have an almost two year old son, so it's when I pick him up at daycare. He is all happy and I am happy too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back to work. It's not so fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:30 a.m. on Wednesday, July 24</pubDate>
				<link>/with/sophie/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/sophie/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Libby</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm shooting a student film, but the actor hasn't shown up yet. So these are some of the guys on the project. The director goes to New York Film Academy and he's waiting for the actor, who's over an hour late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn't usually happen. He's probably panicking more than me though. I'm just sitting here waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;How did you get over here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The F to the R, we met at Union Square and then walked up here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably evening. Usually because I'm done with work. I just like the light, and it cools off in the summer. It's nicer then. Early morning is nice too. I like the less hot parts of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I'm off, so I don't know, we'll see. I don't have to work. I've been doing some time lapse photography with flowers. So I have one flower that will hopefully will open. I did it yesterday, and I had it in the air conditioned living room and it didn't open. The kitchen is near the highway so it shakes. And it had leaves, so I'm going to cut the leaves off so they won't move as much. And I need the sun and the warmth. There's no air conditioning in the kitchen so I think it will open up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;So it's that fast that you can do this in one day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well it depends on the flower. I tried a flower outside in my garden from 6:30 to 9:30, but my camera starting overheating and it barely moved. I picked this dahlia and it's just really slow to open. Some I think will open. We'll see, I just started. This is my second flower. Hopefully I'll get some good stuff. I'm getting that flicker problem. Have you done time lapse before?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Not really. Is it shaking?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's not that it's shaking, it's the light changing. It reads like a flicker. I did one minute intervals yesterday, for about 7 or 8 hours. I kept it on the same exposure. The first time I did it — I just started doing these and if you change the shutter, I was changing to shutter to change exposure which was a big mistake. That was the first time I did it though. And I didn't do any research, it was kind of stupid. I just read how to use the intervalometer. But anyway, yesterday everything was consistent. I think the intervals are too long though so it fluctuates and it reads like a flicker. But it looked kind of cool. Even though nothing moved, the flower kind of breathed and went up and came back down. So yeah, I'm going to do that tomorrow. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:10 a.m. on Wednesday, July 24</pubDate>
				<link>/with/libby/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/libby/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Chris</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just hanging out here for a couple of minutes. I start work at 10 on 27th street So I biked down this morning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm an acupuncturist. I've been doing it for seven years. I broke my back when I was 21 and that was the only thing that helped. I didn't end up getting surgery, but that was the only thing that was able to get the pain to go away. I was going to be a doctor before that, but after acupuncture worked, I was like &quot;fuck this shit, this is cool, I gotta learn how to do acupuncture so I can help people.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;So it was that effective that you went and did it yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yeah. Well, a lot of times in medicine, they're like, &quot;hey, let's see.&quot; It's someone listening to your problems, if something works even a little bit, it's a huge progress in the right direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you enjoy it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love it. It's a lot of work sometimes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I've been around Chelsea for the whole time. I've been in the office I'm at for four years now. But I'm moving in a couple of weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up this morning?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;6am&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you live by yourself?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I live with my fiancée.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the morning. And then the 15 minutes before I go to sleep. It's peaceful. In the morning I get to set up the intention of how the whole day is going to go and what I want to create. And at night it's nice to reflect on it and see what worked and what didn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, I have another office up in Westchester so I'll wake up early and drive up there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;You're not biking up there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, but one of these days I'm going to. It's only like 26 miles and there's a path. I'm in Mount Kisco so you can take the bike path all the way up the Saw Mill. They just don't have a shower up there, so it's been way to hot to just show up and start talking to people all sweaty. There's been days that have been bad. The A/C broke a couple weeks ago and I'm like blotting myself off with paper towels. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:20 a.m. on Wednesday, July 24</pubDate>
				<link>/with/chris/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/chris/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Robert</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m on my lunch break right now. I work in this building over here. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you enjoy it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What’s your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five minutes before 4pm. Work ends and I get to go home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same exact thing. It’s like that movie, Groundhog Day, everything is the same, every day. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:55 p.m. on Wednesday, July 17</pubDate>
				<link>/with/robert/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/robert/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Richard</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm waiting for my wife who has a 12:30 appointment in this building over there. Then we're going to go home we’ll cook some dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh man, I woke up at 5:30 this morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Is that when you leave for work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, that's when I head out of the house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Where do you live?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We live out by Coney Island. We took the subway here today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;12 noon. That’s when I go to prayer at the church over on Fulton. I like it. It keeps me focused and away from the shenanigans in the street.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:10 p.m. on Wednesday, July 17</pubDate>
				<link>/with/richard/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/richard/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Muhammad</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m working here. Selling hotdogs, waters, gatorades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;How long have you been doing this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 week. I’ve been in this country for 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up this morning?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I woke up at 8am. Then I took the subway here. I clean my stand, wipe it down and then my boss brings it here. I’ve been here one week, my boss was on this corner for four years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you enjoy this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I enjoy having a job. In this country people are just lucky to have a job. So I’m happy that I have this. Before, when I didn’t have a job, my head was all over the place. But now I’m focused.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:45 p.m. on Wednesday, July 17</pubDate>
				<link>/with/muhammad/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/muhammad/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
	</channel>
</rss>