<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>On a Wednesday - Articles</title>
		<description></description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feed.articles.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Chris</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m actually working, but I’m on lunch break. I work in a machine shop. We fabricate everything. Just whatever needs to be fabricated, we make it. After that, I’ll usually hang out with friends. But on a Wednesday, I’ll probably just get some sleep. It’s too hot to hang out with friends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I would say right now. This is my favorite part of the day. I don’t have this view where I’m at. I get to come out here, catch the breeze and look at the skyline. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same thing. Nothing really changes until the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:25 p.m. on Wednesday, July 9</pubDate>
				<link>/with/chris/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/chris/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Kevin</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m doing my exercise. I’m chanting and praying. I’m between jobs, but I’m starting to teach yoga on the beach in front of my building in the mornings. But, whatever the day brings, a little bit of reading, it’s hard to say from one day to the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably night time. Living in Rockaway, when the sun goes down it gets cooler, it’s quieter. After the heat of the day, it’s more pleasant for me at night. But mornings are nice too. Before the crowds, before the heat kicks in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably the same. Right now I’m in a funk. I’m fifty six years old and I’m trying to stay healthy. I’ve had some physical problems over the last few years, my shoulders, my joints. I was a lifeguard for many years on the ocean. In Riis Park and in Rockaway. But because of my physical limitation I can’t go back this year. So that’s why I’m going through a change of life right now. I’m sure it will work itself out, but you know, it takes time to figure out what I’m going to do next. But that’s kind of the exciting part, really. I don’t know what I’m going to be doing next. We’ll see what happens. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve done the same thing for so long, maybe it’s time for a change. You know, life is about change. Even to accept growing old and to die, a change of body, a change of life. So it’s something I’ll probably have to deal with eventually, I might as well start dealing with it now. I leave it up to the higher power. What control do I have? I pray for some direction on where I’m going to go next. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:40 a.m. on Wednesday, June 25</pubDate>
				<link>/with/kevin/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/kevin/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Liv</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I’m going to go surfing. I’m busy at about five, so I figure if I come in the morning, I’ll catch three, four hours and have a pretty good day from here on out. They conditions are supposed to be the best today and tomorrow, but a lot of people are scared off by this little bit of fog and rain. But hey, if I’m already in the water, what’s a couple more drops going to do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of my buddies wanted to come out with me. I’m the only one that actually surfs. They heard it was crummy weather and they’re like, not even for that will we sit on the beach. Surfing is like my version of yoga, it’s my me time. So I’m not too offended. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honestly, whenever I get a couple of hours to get out here. I snowboard too, so I’m transitioning from my snowboarding season to my surfing season. It’s always my favorite part of the year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just graduated high school, so all my friends and I are going to go hang by the pool tomorrow and pretend like we’re fancy, reading Cosmo and drinking fruity beverages. It’ll be fun. I actually just signed a modeling contract with an agency based out of Manhattan. So I’m not going to college right away, I’ll be doing that for a little bit, which will be a lot of fun. Because honestly, I’m not too sure what I want to do with my life and college is a $50,000 commitment for something I’m unsure of. I figured, why not? It’ll be fun!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:25 a.m. on Wednesday, June 25</pubDate>
				<link>/with/liv/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/liv/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Kip</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Umm, today I’m running around trying to get paperwork from one place, one doctors office to another doctors office because I have knee surgery on the third. So, I have to provide it before they can determine whether the surgery, they can do it, and whether the cause of the surgery for my knee is coming from here, here, or here [points to hip and back]. That’s the other thing I’m doing today.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When no one else is around. The quietest part, well, I mean, that’s a hard question. The quietest part, after all the nightclubs cool down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m putting together a business, so getting back to work on that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:42 a.m. on Wednesday, June 18</pubDate>
				<link>/with/kip/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/kip/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Gabby</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I’m promoting for the Hudson Project. It’s a music festival in upstate New York. It’s three days with camping. I have to do it secretly because I don’t know if I’m allowed to do this. I don’t know if it’s legal. Well I don’t know if you can hang up posters in New York City. Wouldn’t it be street art? If I’m allowed to put up posters for advertising, but graffiti artists can’t put up their work without getting arrested. I don’t get it. So now I just put these up, take a picture and then bounce. So even if they do take it down, I still get free tickets.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I get to go home and relax. After this I might do my aerial class, silk dancing when the sun goes down. I might do that. If I don’t make the class, I have to go to work in Tribeca. But I have to go all the way up to Queens and then come all the way back down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s where you tie yourself into the silk. The way you tie, is the way you can fall. You fall and unravel yourself. I just started. My friend has been doing it for a few years and she taught me how to do some. I hula hoop dance with fire and LED lights, so I’m trying to do things that can get me other jobs in performing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow is my day off. I hear it’s going to rain, so it’s either go to the aquarium or go out to dinner. I’m taking someone out on a date and I don’t want to stay in my house just yet. I want to hang out in the city. I don’t want to go to a movie. I’d rather talk and have a conversation. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:23 a.m. on Wednesday, June 18</pubDate>
				<link>/with/gabby/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/gabby/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Rose</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think I’m going to bike into Williamsburg and Bushwick. I’m going to head out there tonight to do some street art, so I wanted to scope out a few spots. I’m a printmaker. I do silkscreening, so I made some posters. I’m from San Francisco, just out here for a few weeks. I just picked up my friend’s bike this morning. I biked over here and I’m scoping out the best way to get over there. I might do the bridge and go into Manhattan, but I might just explore those neighborhoods by bike. I brought my lunch and I’m just sort of ready for an adventure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love mornings. The potential, the energy of the mornings. I have really good energy in the mornings. I feel really up and ready to go. And then I also really like warm nights. That’s the best, it’s really invigorating. You don’t really get that in San Francisco, so it’s just a novel experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have no idea. That’s kind of what happens when you’re on vacation. I want to go to the Guggenheim, I haven’t done that yet. So I think I might try to do that. I might check out a few other neighborhoods, I’ve never been to Harlem, never been to Queens. So maybe I’ll bike around and see a few new neighborhoods. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>10:50 a.m. on Wednesday, May 28</pubDate>
				<link>/with/rose/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/rose/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Denise</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m walking dogs. From 8:30 to around 3:30, Monday through Friday. Weekends I’m off. It started as a side thing, because I’m a retired police officer. I love it. It’s really fun. The dogs are sometimes better than hanging out with people. They go with the flow. In general, I pick up the dog and walk it for a half hour or an hour, depending on what the customer wants. I have the same dogs pretty much every day. The clients like that consistency, and the dogs like it too. I get my schedule, I do what I’ve got to do and I don’t have a boss looking over my shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d say the afternoon. Everyone has already gone to work and you’re not dealing with people trying to get the kids to school and getting to work. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same thing, same schedule.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>10:28 a.m. on Wednesday, May 28</pubDate>
				<link>/with/denise/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/denise/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Joelle</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re taking a Tai Chi sword class with Rebecca, our teacher. This is our first time in the park, usually we’re in her loft. We’re all excited that we beat the rain. I was teaching earlier and I’m going to teach right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day is different, so it depends on what that day entails. If it’s a day when I don’t teach first period, but I teach second period, I like that day. Coming home knowing there’s a glass of wine waiting for me as I enter the house. I like that. Weekends are pretty nice, when you don’t work. But each day is different. Today was a good day. My favorite part is right now, doing Tai Chi in the park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’m teaching full time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>5:09 p.m. on Wednesday, May 21</pubDate>
				<link>/with/joelle/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/joelle/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Pam</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re here to buy. We’ve been coming here for almost twenty years and I’m here with my daughter. She’s eleven now and she’s been coming here since she was in me, so it’s a family tradition. We took her out of school, but we felt like this was a really good education. That’s why we come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason why I’m standing right here, is that I’m waiting for a friend and she has a son, he's five and his name is Crosby. He is so precious. He’s only allowed to have ice cream once a year. That once a year is here in Brimfield. Today is the big day. I’m waiting to meet up with them so I can watch him enjoy his once a year ice cream. That’s why I’m standing right in the middle of Heart of the Mart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re supposed to leave today. I called the school and told them that she wasn’t going to be there. But I’m hoping that my husband is like “Well, we’re having such a nice time,” because he’s here the whole week. We came in separate cars. So I’m like, maybe I’ll just take her out of school for the whole week. So that’s kind of on the burner, otherwise we’ll have to leave.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>2:31 p.m. on Wednesday, May 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/pam/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/pam/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Eddie</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m waiting to start a meeting. I volunteer for an organization that helps to provide housing and services people with mental illness. It’s called The Bridge and it’s been around for about 50 years. I serve on one of the boards to help create events to raise money and awareness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier, my friend is leaving for Europe on a bike trip, so I was helping him pack up his bike. Then we stopped to say hi to his sister’s dog. Then I got breakfast and I went to work for a couple hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would have to be really early in the morning or the sunset, because the colors are really pretty and everything feels alive around then. I like the morning because it’s quiet and I can get a lot done before everyone starts moving around. The air is usually a little crisper and cleaner in the morning. I live in Brooklyn and sometimes in the morning you can smell salt in the air from the ocean. Sometimes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well my work is kind of rain related, so if it rains I’ll probably stay home and work on my friend’s bike. I told her I’d fix it and I’m behind on that. If not, I’ll go to work. I’m an engineer and I work in consulting so if it’s raining, they call off work for the day and I have to find something else to do. It’s not so bad.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>5:43 p.m. on Wednesday, May 7</pubDate>
				<link>/with/eddie/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/eddie/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Ryan</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m doing some work. I just came from TechCrunch Disrupt, which is a technology conference. I do public relations for startups. I’m chasing a few interviews for my clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twilight. When the sun is setting, I know that my work is about to be done and I can relax a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s tomorrow? Thursday? I don’t have a full work day tomorrow. This conference ends today. So I’ll still be working, I freelance from home, but I won’t be working as hard as today. I’ll probably be sitting back out here, but minus the laptop.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>5:17 p.m. on Wednesday, May 7</pubDate>
				<link>/with/ryan/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/ryan/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Charlie</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well I’m a retired guy, and I went to a senior center for lunch and talked to some people. I left there and took a long walk, but it’s really windy today. I walked to Eighth Avenue because I wanted to go to the Joyce Theater. It’s a theater known for dance. I just was inquiring about their spring season. Now I’m heading towards Sixth Avenue to do a little shopping. Nothing much today. I’m busy Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It all depends on who I’m with. I would say the afternoons. Mornings I tend to be home. I do a number of things, taking my time reading the paper, maybe have the TV on. I get out in the afternoon. I’ll go to the senior center, not all the days, it depends. I have various activities at the senior center too. It all depends on the schedule that they have. So I spend some time over there. Afterwards I return home, maybe have an activity in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m going to the movies and then a Ukrainian restaurant on the East side.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>4:23 p.m. on Wednesday, April 30</pubDate>
				<link>/with/charlie/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/charlie/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Evan</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today is my first day of learning how to be a pit… person, pit rat, pit professional. It’s a long road. I’ve been with Hometown [Bar-B-Que] since the beginning and I’ve been doing carving for them. It’s been a great experience. I’ve been a cook for a while now, about three years. It’s been seven months at Hometown. Now we’re at the point where we need more people cooking and I’m next in line to learn the sacred art, as it were. It’s pretty awesome. It’s something I’ve been looking forward to in a lot of ways. Partly because it’s a different part of my personality I get to embrace. I’ve been talking to people a lot, I’ve been outgoing. I’m willing to pull part of that back, there are other ways I can do that. But the restaurant is an interesting place; the barbeque community is an interesting set of people. Honestly, the really interesting customers are the ones who are making barbeque at home. Those are the guys who are coming in and they really want to know everything about what you’re doing because they want to do it themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='/with/ernie'&gt;Ernie&lt;/a&gt; is actually a pretty avid fan of the stuff we’re doing. It’s cool to see the stuff that he’s doing compared to the stuff that we’re doing. That’s one of the best parts about barbeque, it’s collaborative. There’s no hiding any secrets, there’s no pretension even, at least not in the circles that I’ve been running in. You just see a lot of really great people who are into the food they’re making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Why is that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s something really friendly about barbecue. I could see some people who are willing to keep it away. But Billy, our pitmaster said, if someone wants a recipe, just give it to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;You don’t see that as competition?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Definitely not. No matter what I tell you about brisket, you are probably going to take a long time before you learn how to do it the right way. The recipe is literally just salt and pepper. It’s more about the technique. The shape that the fire is right now is reflective of what it was an hour ago. You have to know how much you’re adding and why you’re adding it. If you’re going to dampen the box, you have to understand why you’re doing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, the whole idea with the fire is that every fifteen minutes or so, if you’re not keeping on top of it, you’re going to have a drop in temperature. You have to be constantly adding wood.The nature of it is that it’s a very hot fire and it burns the wood quickly, but it has a very clean smoke. That’s one of the big things about barbeque, you want a clean fire. To keep a clean fire, you need to keep feeding it. You have to know when to feed the beast, when to hold off. In a lot of ways it looks and feels like just hanging out by the smoker all day. It’s very different from much of the cooking I’ve done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Usually at the end of the day. I tend to be pretty nocturnal. I really enjoy getting out late and a long walk home. Just that exertion, that cool down. I’m done doing what I’m doing for today and now I’m just enjoying a little bit of peace. I like going home and seeing my roommate. It’s a funny thing. We’re pretty close and just hanging out with him, even if we’re not talking to each other, is still pretty excellent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I actually have no fucking clue. I might be here with this guy at two in the morning to do a lunch cook for tomorrow. I may be here doing that, or I may be in the back of the kitchen tomorrow night. I really have no idea.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>2:00 p.m. on Wednesday, April 16</pubDate>
				<link>/with/evan/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/evan/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Ernie</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I worked today. I came in at 5 in the morning, got my guys out by 7 and did a couple of estimates. I have to go home because I have a few estimates done at my house. I’m having some stuff done to my yard. Other than that, I stop and eat wherever I want and run my business. Not much to my life, it’s pretty boring now. If you’d asked me fifteen years ago, it would have been a different story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing my kids. I know that’s not interesting, but that’s my favorite, going home to my kids at the end of the day. My favorite part during the day is just being out and about. I get to visit my customers, do estimates, new prospects, just being out and about everywhere. I’m in Manhattan two days a week, Brooklyn two days a week, Queens, Staten Island, I’m everywhere. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I will be doing pretty much the same thing, but I’ll be training two of my guys. It’s termite season now, so I’ll be training two of my guys to do termite work, drilling and that stuff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:53 p.m. on Wednesday, April 16</pubDate>
				<link>/with/ernie/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/ernie/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Ashley</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This morning I went to work at a bakery/restaurant called Runner &amp;amp; Stone. I went to work at one in the morning. So I got off of work around ten o’clock. And then I went to an art studio. I do oil paintings, and my art studio is a couple of blocks from Runner &amp;amp; Stone, it’s called Brooklyn Art Space in Gowanus. I went there and finished my painting. And then I came here and I’m reading Game of Thrones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to say because I had such an awesome morning baking bread. It was just one of those mornings where everything went really smoothly and I was really happy with my baguette shapes. So that was really good. Also, finishing a painting is a great feeling. It starts off as a blank canvas, so when you’re finished it’s a good feeling. And right now I’m up to a really good part in the book. It’s a beautiful day out, just one of those good days. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have off from work. If it’s this nice, probably just walk around. Walk over the Brooklyn Bridge or do something like that. If it’s not nice out, I’ll spend the day in my art studio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='note small'&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editor's Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Ashley invited us into her home and shared some of her paintings with us. They're delicious and we highly recommend checking out her &lt;a href='http://www.etsy.com/shop/CanvasByAshley'&gt;Etsy shop&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>5:38 p.m. on Wednesday, April 9</pubDate>
				<link>/with/ashley/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/ashley/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Sanna</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going to work at the United Nations. I work in the Conflict Prevention Office. It’s quite interesting. After work I have to pack because I’m traveling tomorrow. I’m going to Finland and then to Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The morning, if it’s sunny and warm. Today it’s at least sunny but it’s not warm. It’s a fresh start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’ll be traveling to Finland. My flight is in the evening, so I’ll be at work and then I’ll be traveling to Finland.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:33 a.m. on Wednesday, March 26</pubDate>
				<link>/with/sanna/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/sanna/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Patrick</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I’m working until 4 o’clock. Then I’ll hit the gym right after work. After that I’ll probably cook dinner. I thought about making pasta and meatballs. And I’ll see my girlfriend. I make my own sauce, so I like to do that on occasion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I leave work. Today is actually payday, so that means I get to go cash my check and pay bills. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have to work from 8:30 until 4, and then probably go to the gym again. No, no I don’t. Tomorrow is my day off! So I’ll probably sleep in, eat junk food, go to the gym and feel guilty about it. That’s about it. I might go out with some friends. I’ll see how it goes. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:27 a.m. on Wednesday, March 26</pubDate>
				<link>/with/patrick/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/patrick/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Gregory</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re doing GPS observation for a mapping project. After Sandy, this area was flooded, so the MTA is looking to protect their underground structures from flooding again. This is part of that project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The view. The view isn’t here on all of the days. I worked in this area like fifteen years ago. It was a dump area, no buildings, just homelessness, dirt and debris. Now look at it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:11 a.m. on Wednesday, March 26</pubDate>
				<link>/with/gregory/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/gregory/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Ariel</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m looking for an address, but someone gave me the wrong address. So I’m waiting for these people to call me back. That’s the reason why I’m here. I’m waiting for the people to call me back and give me the exact address. I’m a window cleaner, so I need the exact address.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll go to some place between 11th and 10th avenues and 34th street to find a place to eat dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’ll start work early, 5 o’clock. After 11 sometimes I have nothing, sometimes I have something. Today I had something. It's early, but I work inside so it’s not so cold.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:17 p.m. on Wednesday, March 12</pubDate>
				<link>/with/ariel/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/ariel/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Eddy</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m up early in the morning, 9 o’clock. I study from 9 o’clock to 1 o’clock. I study Jewish studies. Then I come to the Square and buy some books. Later I’m going to meet my friend to study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I finish studying. I know that I’ve accomplished what I set out to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’m going to study until 1 o’clock, since I’m retired. Then I’ll meet with my daughter for lunch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:04 p.m. on Wednesday, March 12</pubDate>
				<link>/with/eddy/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/eddy/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Patrick</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m heading home to write some music and play some bass. I just came from a coffee shop up on Flatbush called Hungry Ghost. I was working there, pouring some espresso. I do that a few days a week, and otherwise I'm just writing music and playing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably the evening, right around dinner time. I like to cook. My fiance comes home and we make some dinner and drink some wine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow is my day off, so I haven’t really made any plans. We’re leaving the city soon, so I’ll probably take care of some odds and ends, book a U-Haul trailer. We’re from Canada, so we’re heading back to where we’re from. We’ll spend the summer in a Prince Edward Island. It will be a nice break from the city.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:52 p.m. on Wednesday, February 19</pubDate>
				<link>/with/patrick/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/patrick/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Taylor</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m going to the V.A. for an appointment. I have an appointment because I’m ex-military and a purple heart and I lost two toes. So I’m going to the V.A. and I’m going to let them take a look. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I would say the morning. You never know what to expect in New York City. Usually the unexpected comes in the morning. I think it’s because New York is moving so fast, and I believe that the best laid plans get thwarted by New York City in the morning. So you have to revamp, rethink and reschedule. In the morning, I like the hecticness of it. It keeps you on your toes, even if you only have eight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I will probably clean the snow off the roof. It’s supposed to be warm tomorrow, and dry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:14 p.m. on Wednesday, February 19</pubDate>
				<link>/with/taylor/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/taylor/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Saul</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got out of school and I’m about to go rock climbing right now at Brooklyn Boulders and then I’ll come back to school. I’m going to school for mechanical engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I get to go home and sleep. That’s pretty much it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll be up early again to come to school. After school I got to go to work. Then after that, I’ll go home and sleep again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:03 p.m. on Wednesday, February 19</pubDate>
				<link>/with/saul/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/saul/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Allen</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I came down to RadioShack to exchange something that I bought that wasn’t working too well. They gave me back my money. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll probably be back in the studio later. I did two songs for my job. I work at Brooklyn Hospital. I’ve been there for 33 years. I have a big song called TBHC, Keep Brooklyn Healthy, letting everyone know how to get to the hospital, where and how to get there. And also about our E.R. nurses, what they do for you when you come there and how you feel. So I’ll be in the studio later trying finish those up.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d probably say around afternoon. I usually get off around 2. Working in the emergency room it gets a little crazy. Putting out supplies and materials all day long and trauma and everything else going on. But I would say when I get off, I relax a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll actually be going going to work tomorrow and then cooling off for the rest of the day. I’m off next Monday, so I have a couple days off. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:52 p.m. on Wednesday, February 19</pubDate>
				<link>/with/allen/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/allen/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Mike</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm making coffee most of the day. I'll go home, probably watch a little Netflix, and then hang out with my wife. That's basically my day today. Might go out to dinner. What is tonight? It's Wednesday. We'll probably go to Buttermilk Channel. We live in Carroll Gardens, so we'll probably be going there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My afternoon nap. I didn't add that before. I usually watch Netflix as I take my afternoon nap. I take a 15-30 minute power nap. That's my favorite part of the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I'll be here again, making coffee. That will be the extent of my day. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:30 p.m. on Wednesday, February 12</pubDate>
				<link>/with/another-mike/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/another-mike/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Christian</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today we are doing a bunch of different things. We are going to teach some kids how to play chess, how to play chess better. We are going to have an adult commercial chess league later on today that we’re preparing for. And, I will be leaving very shortly to train some of my star trophy winning chess champions in Queens to prepare for the national tournament. So it’s a full day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My favorite part of the day is waking up and strategizing what it is that I want to get accomplished and how I’m going to do it. That’s really my favorite part of the day. It’s like a piece of paper, when you haven’t put anything on it yet. So the possibilities and your imagination run wild, and you’re thinking about all the cool things that you can write or draw or color. That’s basically how I see the day, until I get into it. Then it all changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow is Thursday. Actually tomorrow is a little bit quieter. We have the after-school program, so we’ll be teaching chess to some kids tomorrow afternoon. We won’t be training, we’ll be working with kids who come here after school. We’ll be trying to get them to learn some better strategy and build their self-esteem a lot through chess. The kids that come on Thursday, there are two different groups. We have a very competitive, strong, strategic group of kids. Then we have the beginners, who are still trying to manage staying and paying attention. So Ms. Jillian is one of our best younger teachers. So, she kind of sits with them, but she’s new. So tomorrow we’ll be spending some time just making sure things that she needs to do and watching the kids learn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>2:13 p.m. on Wednesday, February 12</pubDate>
				<link>/with/christian/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/christian/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>James</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I came down to see Verizon about my phone. Somehow, my phone was going straight to voicemail. But I had it on airplane mode. I was telling the guy down there, knowledge is key. I didn’t bother to look at the settings and check airplane mode. Now I now. I learned something today. Later I’ll probably go pick my friend up from work and take him home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The morning, becuse I woke up. A lot of my friends, with the lifestyle I’ve lived are not here today. I am truly grateful for waking up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure. My schedule is that open. I’m definitely looking forward to it. I may jump in the van to help someone move tomorrow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Hopefully it’s not too nasty out tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t bother me. I’ve been through 66 of these things. Come on. I can’t understand the big uproar about the weather. But it’s always been a topic for conversation. In the Northeast, you’ve got to expect this. You think the people in Boston are complaining? This is not bad. The subways are out, people are all confused and discombobulated. Look at the street though, I fail to see the confusion. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:49 p.m. on Wednesday, February 5</pubDate>
				<link>/with/james/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/james/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Cierra</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m at work, selling cosmetic products. Later I’ll be listening to some music, because I love music. I also like to make music. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What kind of music do you make?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;R&amp;amp;B, but I just do it for fun right now. It’s a hobby. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may sound crazy, but it’s the morning. You don’t know how the day is going to start. It’s spontaneous. It’s unknown. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, I’m doing the same thing. Working and networking with people, as usual. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:20 p.m. on Wednesday, February 5</pubDate>
				<link>/with/cierra/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/cierra/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Chris</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now, I’m at work all day today. I work at a retail store, I won’t say which one. But I’m just working today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doing something active. I’m big on fitness, so usually I go to the gym after work or play a little basketball. That’s how I like to end my days. Being 6’4”, you kind of get thrown into sports early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is my day off. So what I usually like to do is start my day at the gym, because that’s the best part. Get myself in a good mood. I’ll probably hang out with some friends. I have a list of things that I want to get done throughout the year, whether that’s going to a good show, or taking a vacation. So I’ll try to cross something off the list.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>2:47 p.m. on Wednesday, January 22</pubDate>
				<link>/with/chris/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/chris/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Zach</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got down here. I’m waiting for my friend. I’m a student at LIM college and we had off today because school’s cancelled. It’s not really that bad out. She’s interviewing for a job around the corner. Not sure what we’re going to do, we’ll probably play it by ear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I guess waking up. It’s a new day, a fresh start. I feel relaxed. Get ready to start the day and do whatever you need to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;School isn’t cancelled tomorrow, so gotta go back to school. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>2:34 p.m. on Wednesday, January 22</pubDate>
				<link>/with/zach/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/zach/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Katie</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m just coming from the Agenda trade show. I wish that my day was ending now, but I’m heading back to my office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking out of the office at the end of the day. Then I get to go off and do whatever I want. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Very similar to today. The trade show is in town and it’s two days, so I’ll be back there. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>2:30 p.m. on Wednesday, January 22</pubDate>
				<link>/with/katie/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/katie/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Joe</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ice skating, then going to Nelson A. Rockefeller Park, then watching a movie. Sort of a good Wednesday. I took off work today, so it should be eventful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably getting home. It’s relaxing. Usually I try to book my days. So I usually go to work and then the gym, maybe meet up with buddies and then just head home. That’s the best part of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also taking off work. My girlfriend is still in school. This is her last week, so I’m just trying to spend all my time with her. I have the next few months to just work my ass of, so that’s what I’ll do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>10:40 p.m. on Wednesday, January 15</pubDate>
				<link>/with/joe/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/joe/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Richelle</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am going over to sign a lease on a new apartment, then going to work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My favorite part of the day is mornings. I spend time reading my bible. It’s very refreshing to me, and revitalizing. That’s how I spend my morning: a cup of coffee and God’s word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’m moving into my new apartment. And then going to work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>10:40 p.m. on Wednesday, January 15</pubDate>
				<link>/with/richelle/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/richelle/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Tom</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m enjoying the view of Bryant Park, watching the skaters go by, enjoying the nice clear day, and enjoying myself.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably when the sun is out and it’s not too cold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably just taking a walk around the city. Enjoying the sites of the Christmas season. I like to walk for exercise instead of staying home all cooped up, watching TV. I like to get out and get some pounds off. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:48 p.m. on Wednesday, December 11</pubDate>
				<link>/with/tom/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/tom/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Victor</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I went to the Apple store to fix my Macbook. It had some problems, so I got it fixed. Now I’m about to meet with my sister. She’s over at 42nd, in Times Square. We were trying to decide if we should meet over there or meet over here. I think she’s going to come over here. So I’m just waiting for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably when I go home after a long day. Just coming home to a home cooked meal is my favorite part of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’ll be taking a final. I have to take a philosophy final. I have to study tonight, it’s going to suck.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:28 p.m. on Wednesday, December 11</pubDate>
				<link>/with/victor/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/victor/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Kenny</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m working at Starbucks. After work I’m going to go do some shopping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leaving work to go home. Just sleep after a long day of work. I get here at 7 in the morning. It’s crazy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;School. It’s finals week and it’s going to be crazy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:20 p.m. on Wednesday, December 11</pubDate>
				<link>/with/kenny/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/kenny/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Yuki &amp; Summer</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just visiting. We wanted to go to the United Nations building but we didn’t buy our tickets. But maybe tomorrow we’ll return to the United Nations building and tonight we’ll buy some tickets. This afternoon we’ll go to the Trinity Church.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grand Central Station. I searched for information on the website and found out about the kissing room. To say goodbye to their parents or their wives or husbands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’ll visit Broadway, the United Nations and Central Park.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:03 p.m. on Wednesday, December 11</pubDate>
				<link>/with/yuki-summer/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/yuki-summer/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Mike</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m selling Christmas trees on 14th street &amp;amp; 9th avenue. Usually I’m here all day. The shifts run 12 or 11 hours. We have another stand over in Brooklyn. They have two shifts a day. One during the day and one at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting here is the easiest, you’re still fresh. By the end of the day, you’re cold and miserable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’ll be back here. Same thing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:21 a.m. on Wednesday, December 4</pubDate>
				<link>/with/mike/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/mike/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Meghan</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m decorating a Christmas tree stand that I’m working at. I’ll decorate the shopping cart that we deliver trees in. Mostly decorating before the rain comes. Opening trees, sweeping, there’s probably more on the list. It’s just a big list of really random Christmas tree stuff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably when I wake up at 6 in the morning. It’s all quiet and no one is around for an hour. I get to sit, drink coffee and think for a second. That’s my favorite part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same things, probably. Maybe more stuff geared towards the weekend. It’s probably going to be the biggest weekend. We’ll have all sorts of varieties of trees out. It’s going to be nuts, in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work from like 6 in the morning until 11 at night. Then the night guy comes and stays up all night for us. It’s a pretty intense month, but it’s good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:21 a.m. on Wednesday, December 4</pubDate>
				<link>/with/meghan/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/meghan/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Billy</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selling Christmas trees. It’s our 26th season on Jane st. Thanksgiving is late this year, so it’s a short season. Man, has it been busy. We’re open 24 hours a day, until midnight on Christmas Eve. We sell or recieve something 24 hours a day. There are three of us, myself, my son and my son in law, and a bunch of neighborhood misfits who help us run the place. Actually, we couldn’t run it without them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We spend eleven months in Vermont and one month is Manhattan. What could be better? Many of my customers are jealous. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My favorite part of a weekday like this is the mornings when I can sit here, drink tea, eat a bagel and greet people and talk. Usually by 10 a.m. it’s very busy. This morning, for some reason, by 8 a.m. it was very busy. So I didn’t get to do my little sit around and eat my bagel thing. But that’s my favorite part of the day. I love it. The sun hits me here. The people are greeting me every five minutes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My favorite part of the whole deal is the people. Meeting the people and the relationships. But this is the Wednesday website, so my favorite part is sitting here and having people say Merry Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’ll be doing the same thing. Same thing, same thing up until midnight on Christmas eve. We’re open 24 hours. I live right here on the corner, until midnight on Christmas eve. I might get a beer or pizza here and there. But mostly it’s right here where we’re standing selling trees. We used to be a small business, now we’re a big business in a small space. It’s very hectic. I have ten or twelve neighborhood kids working for me. It’s a riot here. If you like action, try Saturday morning at 11 o’clock. It’s a zoo here. There’s kids, people, trees, helpers. We got one big shipment of trees at the beginning, and now we get twice a week or more. We fill in with little orders.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:21 a.m. on Wednesday, December 4</pubDate>
				<link>/with/billy/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/billy/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Susie</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m making mini-wreaths for a customer. I’ve just been doing some crafts. I’m not selling many trees, so I’m just making a few things. I start at 5 a.m. and try to go to bed around 9 p.m. It’s just for one month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between 1:30 p.m. and 2:30 p.m., I get the sun right there. That’s my favorite part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same thing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:03 a.m. on Wednesday, December 4</pubDate>
				<link>/with/susie/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/susie/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Taka</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm visiting the famous spots in NY today. I'm from Tokyo on a trip alone for the first time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today is the 4th day but the last day of my trip. Since it's sunny, I enjoyed the scapes of SOHO, and I've come here, the Brooklyn Bridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any time with plenty of sunlight. I love drinking coffee with views of Central park and Danvo in the Sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm going to leave NY at 10:30 a.m. for Tokyo. I've been so excited and inspired by NY and New Yorkers so far. This visiting makes me feel like challenging everything everyday for the rest of my life. I wonder if I'll have another chance to come to NY again and work in in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>10:53 a.m. on Wednesday, November 20</pubDate>
				<link>/with/taka/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/taka/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Kay &amp; Joe</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’ve just come across from the Statue of Liberty. We went on the helicopter tour this morning. We’re going to Ground Zero this afternoon. We’re just going over to Brooklyn now to get some lunch. Then we’ll hop back across for the 9/11 memorial and some Chinatown. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’ve just put a lock on the side here. It’s similar to the one that they’ve got in France. The bridge where you throw away the key to symbolize everlasting love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well the helicopter ride was the best. We got to see everything from there. We got a bit of an idea of the layout. Times Square is pretty breathtaking. Quite intense. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think we’re going to do the Empire State Building tomorrow. And then just some shopping on 5th Avenue. We’re here for 6 days. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:50 a.m. on Wednesday, November 20</pubDate>
				<link>/with/kay-joe/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/kay-joe/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Monika</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re going over the Brooklyn Bridge, to spend our afternoon there before we go back to Germany. Later we’ll go to the airport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bridge, of course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow we have off. We’ll relax with jetlag.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:30 a.m. on Wednesday, November 20</pubDate>
				<link>/with/monika/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/monika/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Bettina</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m going to check out Manhattan. I got here yesterday, so we’re walking here, then to check out the 9/11 Memorial. Hope to get some dim sum in Chinatown, then maybe walk the High Line. I’m a tourist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably when I come home from work to see my girls. I have two girls. I get home from work, it’s been a decent day at the office. I get home and see them and disconnect for a few hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m going to go to the MoMA. Walk a little bit, see a bit of 5th Avenue and that whole area. Probably going to walk around the East Village. I’m not really sure, but I’ll definitely go see the MoMA.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:22 a.m. on Wednesday, November 20</pubDate>
				<link>/with/bettina/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/bettina/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>George</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m cooking lamb and chicken for anybody. It’s good. I’ve been here since one or two o'clock. They have the bar here, everybody after they finish their drink, comes here to eat. I come here around 7 pm, until around one or two o’clock. If it’s busy, 2 o’clock. This cart is not mine. I work for three bosses. I work here and I work in a garage down the street, four blocks from here. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cart here is the best, everyone tells me. I love everybody and everybody loves me. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work at night. I see everybody here. These are my customers, I’ve worked here for two years. I know everybody here, and everybody knows me. I joke around with everybody like this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work tomorrow. It will rain tomorrow, so business will be slow. When you have rain or snow, I’ll see like ten or twenty customers. Everyone is at home. Tomorrow I’ll leave early because of the rain. My boss tells me there’s no business in the rain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:06 p.m. on Wednesday, November 06</pubDate>
				<link>/with/george/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/george/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Bob</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m here after work. This is my friends’ place. It’s the biggest sports bar in Brooklyn. I came to get something to eat and talk to a couple people, see if they were interested in helping out and donating some time for the kids. It’s the &lt;a href='https://www.facebook.com/SecretSandyClausProject'&gt;Secret Sandy Clause project&lt;/a&gt;. If you know someone that needs a toy, you put down a toy that they want and they will get it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I guess when I wake up and have nothing to do. I can just kick back and grab a newspaper, grab a book and just relax. They are very far and few between.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow is an ordeal. I’m off tomorrow. I’ll go see my granddaughter and daughter tomorrow. It’s a great day. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>11:06 p.m. on Wednesday, November 06</pubDate>
				<link>/with/bob/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/bob/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Kenshasa</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I’m walking my dog in the park, I have a couple of appointments, and I have a meeting later on this evening. I am an international distributor of organic coffee and teas. I have meetings today around that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh actually this is one of my favorite parts of the day. Just getting out into the fresh air, the morning air, before all the fumes get into it. Having Fudge [the dog] interact with other pets, it’s just wonderful. I enjoy it very much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I have a workshop. I’m a psychologist and I do workshops on stress management. So I have a workshop tomorrow at 8:30 in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:51 a.m. on Wednesday, October 23</pubDate>
				<link>/with/kenshasa/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/kenshasa/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Frank</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had breakfast already, in the park here. And now after I finish doing this crossword puzzle and the rest of the paper, I’ll go and get another paper and do the crossword puzzle. Then I’m going to take a long walk into Williamsburg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m new to this area, so I like to walk, and walk, and walk. I’ll take a three hour walk this afternoon. I’m looking for something. I walked by it one day. On any one of the streets, just between Kent and Bedford. And, I came by a little theater that looked interesting, but I didn’t note it. So now I’m searching the streets. I’ve got to go find it. I started yesterday, did about three hours, walking around and I still have about eight more streets to do there. It looked like it was very small. So I want to catch that and see what their schedule is, and what they have there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I moved from Manhattan. Actually, I’ll tell you the whole story. I used to live on 36th St. And the guy, I knew he was having problems with the building, it was a five story walkup. And he kept on renovating the building, and not reporting it to the proper people. He’d be selling it to members of his family, so he’d have to start all over again.  So, finally the judge got fed up, told the Buildings Department and the Fire Department, go over there and if it’s illegal, shut it down. Out of about twenty apartments, there was only one legal apartment. And the fireman said to me, “it’s not yours.” So the Red Cross put us up in a hotel for two days and now I’m living at the Y, trying to save enough money to get an apartment. But hey, a lot of people have it worse than me. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I like this neighborhood, and I don’t think I can afford Manhattan anymore. So I’ve got to wait another couple of weeks, save some more money, and go to a real estate agent. I’ve gone to a couple to get an idea, and if I can’t find anything here, my niece lives in Astoria. She says “Uncle Frank, we’ve got plenty of room over here.” I used to go out with a girl there, so I know the area. I’ve hung out in it, what have you. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But here I like it. If I had all my stuff with me, I’d be working out for two hours in the morning. Jogging, pushups against the bench, I have these weights that I walk with and jog with. So I like to be near McCarren Park. There are other small parks, but the thing that keeps me going, like when I lived on the west side of Manhattan, I’d go up the river one time, and down the river the next day. It keeps you going. Here I can go around different trails and they’ve got the track over there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s my story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the late afternoon, when I sit down and have a few beers with some people around here. I’ve only been here six weeks and I’m already treated like family by a lot of people. I like the people here. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If I don’t find that today, I’m going to repeat it again until I find it. But I think I’ll find it today. If not, I’m going to go see the Tom Hanks movie tomorrow afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:00 a.m. on Wednesday, October 16</pubDate>
				<link>/with/frank/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/frank/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Kristin</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well I’m on vacation. I used to live here. And I’m actually walking now from Greenpoint, I think it’s Clay street. So, I’m walking all the way across the Williamsburg Bridge. I really have no plans. I’m choosing to not hang out with people and just kind of see where the day goes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My favorite part of the day is morning, definitely. It’s kind of quiet and cozy. People are just getting going, so it’s a good time to think and walk and look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well tonight I’m actually headed up to Cape Cod with friends from the city. We’re going to go up there for a few days. I live in Northern Michigan, Traverse City. I was in the city for ten years, and then after 9/11 I just wanted to go settle elsewhere. So I did! &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:57 a.m. on Wednesday, October 16</pubDate>
				<link>/with/kristin/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/kristin/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Rob</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obviously attending Brooklyn Beta. Also visiting Brooklyn while I’m in town for a team meeting at Editorially. That’s my day today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting to hang out with a lot of good friends that I don’t get to see very often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brooklyn Beta, again. Pretty much the same thing, but I think I’m going to start off the day with a nice, long run through Prospect Park, which will be nice. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>3:31 p.m. on Wednesday, October 9</pubDate>
				<link>/with/rob/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/rob/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Jay</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m at Brooklyn Beta. This is my first time, so I’m sort of figuring it out as it goes. It’s been fun. Nice to meet people and talk a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hard to say. Lunch was great. A friend of mine from Chicago is here, and  I noticed him and we ate lunch together. It was nice to catch up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll be here again tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>3:35 p.m. on Wednesday, October 9</pubDate>
				<link>/with/jay/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/jay/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Scott</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m going to go to work later on. I teach. I’m going to go teach some courses, and then I’m going to go work on some projects this afternoon, some articles that I’m working on.  I teach media and communications. I teach advertising. I teach public relations. I teach mass communications. And I write, I have to write. I have to publish this stuff. It is pretty much a good day. Every day is a good day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a morning person. I enjoy the mornings more. I like to take it easy in the morning and then work later on in the day. And I get more work done in the evening than I do in the morning. That’s just a habit I’ve had in life for a long time. I like to work late in the night. I usually stay in my office until after midnight most often. I like coming out in the morning, there aren’t many folks around. I come out of my office, there aren’t many folks around. I don’t have anything against people, I like people. But the kind of work I do, just by nature, I spend a lot of time alone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s pretty solitary work. You’re either spending time reading other people’s works, that’s how you get to know people, is basically through their writing, or you’re spending time with your own thoughts. I think that’s almost a danger of the job, is that you spend too much time with your own thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similar schedule.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:28 a.m. on Wednesday, October 2</pubDate>
				<link>/with/scott/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/scott/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Ann</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well since it’s Indian summer, I’m taking more time in the morning to be outside and workout, although I have a lot of work to do. And I’m also on Pan American Organization, the translation committee, so half the day we’ll be in Manhattan, and then I’ll go to a meeting this evening. So half the day in Brooklyn, half the day in Manhattan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The morning. Always. I like the light, I like the cooler temperature if it’s a warmer season. It always seems hopeful. I have this big shoot of energy around 2:30, and then I come out of that and then I’m better in the early evening. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m taking care of admin stuff today. So I’ll get back to poetry tomorrow. It’s best in the morning, writing poetry. I do believe in the idea that when you wake up, you’re still open to some other sort of dream world and everything that is still going on in your subconscious, so it’s an effective time to write. And you don’t listen to the radio or bring in the bad news before you start.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:33 a.m. on Wednesday, October 2</pubDate>
				<link>/with/ann/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/ann/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Kirby</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:40 a.m. on Wednesday, October 2</pubDate>
				<link>/with/kirby/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/kirby/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Ed</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working. I work at the Beastly Bites over there, the pet food and supply store. I manage it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going home to see my son.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same thing. Monday through Friday, same routine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:55 a.m. on Wednesday, October 2</pubDate>
				<link>/with/ed/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/ed/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Peter</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just took a ride around Manhattan on a bike. I already worked out in the morning, so I ran out of gas after 20 miles. So I’m taking the ferry back. I didn’t feel like going back over the 59th Street Bridge. I can handle it, but it’s too hot now. I came over the 59th Street Bridge, and went over through Central Park and then over to the West Side Highway and picked up the ferry over here to go back to Long Island City, where I live. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m going to go home and check on my dog, and then he has to go for grooming at 3 p.m. Then I’ll go for dinner later in the city with my girlfriend. It’s  a day off, you gotta enjoy it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably just about right now. Being outside is great and this ferry ride helps to cool off. By the time I get off I won’t be sweaty anymore. So this is the best part of the day, right here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have to go back to work, so I won’t be out here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:40 p.m. on Wednesday, September 11</pubDate>
				<link>/with/peter/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/peter/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Josefine</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m on a visit. A ferry ride, just came from the heat in New York. I’m going to the Staten Island ferry. Sight seeing, I just want to get out of Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later, I don’t have plans really. I just decide continuously what I feel like doing. Go in a restaurant, have some lunch, how I feel. No stress, no time pressure on vacation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For me, it’s breakfast time. Entering the coffee shop, relax and drink a coffee. Start the day in a relaxed way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have no idea. I think I will decide tomorrow morning. Take the city map and what will come, I don’t know yet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:52 p.m. on Wednesday, September 11</pubDate>
				<link>/with/josefine/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/josefine/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>David</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m seeing city sights all day. I started off on 51st st., in Midtown. I was planning to visit Williamsburg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe the sunset. That hour of the day. The temperature is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, maybe seeing the upper part of the city. Central Park, and Riverside Park.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:57 p.m. on Wednesday, September 11</pubDate>
				<link>/with/david-2/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/david-2/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Susie</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m watering my plants here. It’s turned out to be a beautiful day here in the hot sun. So, I have to haul a lot of water in because I’m at an antique show and they need tender, loving care. I’m the plant lady at this show. I’ve been doing it for 20 years or more. So I have a lot of repeat customers. I’m known for my plants and other things. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Are you here all day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I’m here all week. I’ve been here since Saturday, setting up. I’m here until Saturday or Sunday. It depends on how much I sell and what the weather is like. I’m here for the duration. I never leave early. Nobody leaves from this field. Other fields, people will stay for a few hours or a day. We all stay. We’re very committed to everyone staying here. We have customers all week long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What’s your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just love it all. I absolutely do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m happy when I wake up. I sleep here too. I sleep either in my van with my little dog, Ted. Or we sleep in a tent in the back. We’re very happy. We’re happy when we wake up. I make coffee. Fresh ground beans. I know how to travel. And I love seeing my customers. I have a lot of repeat customers, because I’ve been here so long. So I love seeing them again. It’s more than business, we hug. We talk about real things going on in our lives. It’s friendships over years. I’m happy all day long. By the end of the day, I’m happy to have a glass of wine and I have dinner with friends. We either do something here on the field or we go to a nearby restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same thing. Same old, same old. You know, water the plants, take good care of them so that they look really good. Bag up some more potpourri. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You know, I’m constantly redecorating the booth, moving things around. This table has been there a while, move that, maybe move this over, change things on top of the tables. They look different placed in a different arrangement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love this booth because it has shrubbery around it and it kind of goes with my stuff. I’m really happy in this space. I tried other fields before finding this one, and I’m really happy here. And this is my gypsy family. We convene, we gather as a group. It’s very sad at the end of September Brim, because we won’t see each other until May. We keep in touch with email or Facebook, but it’s not like being together. I’m very fond of my neighbors. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>2:07 p.m. on Wednesday, September 4</pubDate>
				<link>/with/susie/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/susie/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Betsy</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What am I doing? I’m hanging out in Brimfield. I had a little bit of fun though. I’m going to be here all day. I’ll be here until Sunday. It’s an awful lot of work. So when you get tired and discouraged, you just have fun. You go to your neighbors, you steal some letters, you spell out some things. As long as it’s not too naughty. I don’t want to get kicked out of the field. But it’s a beautiful day. It’s gorgeous out. I people watch too while I’m here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t know how many years I’ve been coming here, you’ll have to ask one of these other folks. I shopped here 30 years ago. This might be year number six that I’ve actually set up here. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I like first thing in the morning. I get up at like 4. Nobody else is up, it’s quiet, it’s dark. I have my coffee and I can take my time to set up and do my thing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same thing. I might do a little shopping tomorrow. Just in this field, this is the best field. It’s just comfortable, it’s easy going, not just straight rows of tents. I think this used to be a campsite. I get along with everybody in here. Everybody is pretty cool in this field. It’s only sometimes the patrons are fighting with each other. It’s entertainment. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>2:20 p.m. on Wednesday, September 4</pubDate>
				<link>/with/betsy/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/betsy/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Carl</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm going to work. I'm an attorney.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What’s your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going home. Because work stinks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:23 a.m. on Wednesday, August 28</pubDate>
				<link>/with/carl/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/carl/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Brian</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm working until 10 this morning, then probably go home and take a nap because I was here at 6. And then I have a basketball game at 6:45, then I'll probably go out after to some party at 9:30. And then I have school in the morning, so that's it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What’s your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably the nap part. It's relaxing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have school. First day of school at Queensboro.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:36 a.m. on Wednesday, August 28</pubDate>
				<link>/with/brian/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/brian/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Jamel</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm working for MTA, doing customer service. I'm letting everyone know that there is no R service going Brooklyn bound. I'll be here until around 12:20 - 12:30. I've been here for two weeks straight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work general field, so I could be anywhere. I could be at a station, giving information on how to get to your destination, or I can be riding on the bus, doing a ride check. So I could be doing anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What’s your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting off. I actually work two jobs, so I leave here and go to another one. Everyday I work two jobs besides Thursdays, Fridays, Saturdays and Sundays. Because Thursday and Friday are my days off with the MTA, and then I'm a custodian at PS179 and my days off are Friday, Saturday there. I need to rest at least two or three hours in a day. Sometimes I'm just tired. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I'll be working as a custodian. Just a custodian tomorrow. But Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, it's pretty competitive with the two jobs. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:30 a.m. on Wednesday, August 28</pubDate>
				<link>/with/jamel/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/jamel/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Aimee</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm going to go to college at the college of Staten Island. I'm studying biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What’s your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I get home. Because I'm going to be late to my house. I'll be really tired. I just study two days, from the morning to the night. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:20 a.m. on Wednesday, August 28</pubDate>
				<link>/with/aimee/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/aimee/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Ken</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lunch break. Yep, work and lunch. I work for the courts system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This right here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going home first, this is second. Because leaving the city for the suburbs or Staten Island is more my style than being here in the city and working in Downtown Brooklyn. So this is a nice escape here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably the same thing. Going to work, coming down here if it’s nice out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:40 p.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/ken/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/ken/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Eiko</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just hanging around, it’s a nice day. Just walked from home here, and I was going to walk over the little swinging bridge, but it’s closed. Usually I don’t come around here. Usually I go Pier 6. I think they’re working on the bridge, maybe it’s too swingy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late afternoon. Right before dinner, it’s not so cold, it’s not so hot.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow will be a nice day too, so I might be out for a little bit. I usually go to the gym, but today was a nice day so I wanted to enjoy it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:35 p.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/eiko/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/eiko/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Rashad</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, right now I’m working for the DEP, so it’s just another day at work. After this, I’m planning to go home. I’m not really sure what I’m going to do. Hopefully find something fun to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I live in Staten Island. So it will take me a few hours to get home from here. Around two, usually. Hope this will help me out in the future, getting a permanent job at the DEP. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a summer internship. I started in early May and it will end around mid-August. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My job entails coming to one of these fountains at a certain location, usually at Brooklyn Bridge, City Hall, or Union Square. We just tell the public about the benefits of New York City water. Try to get them to use tap water instead of bottled water, to help preserve the environment, not waste so much plastic and money. Especially living in the New York, the tap water is so great. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d like to say the end of the day, because it gets kind of tiring standing out here for about seven or eight hours a day lecturing people. It has it’s perks, but the end of the work day is definitely my favorite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’m working at Union Square. I’ll be there around 9:30. And at night I have  a birthday party to go to up in Queens at a hookah lounge. So, that should be fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:30 p.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/rashad/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/rashad/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Chris</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m just on my lunch break right now. I’ve got about an hour left, so I’m just taking it easy. I work in a finance firm in DUMBO and we do a lot of work with financing for copy machines and green energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Favorite part of the day is when I go home. I’m a runner, so I like to run at night. It kinds of gets in the way of work, but what can you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same thing. Working, coming out here for lunch if it’s nice out. Then hopefully tomorrow night, I’ll take my girlfriend out to dinner.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:40 p.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/chris/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/chris/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Earle</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Playing bridge, as soon as my compadres come. I'm retired, so I can do whatever I want. I'll be here until about four o'clock, that's when we finish. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I wake up. Because God has been good to me, I'm not dead. That's my favorite part of any day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;God willing, playing bridge and counting my money. Then I'll get on my phone and call my lawyer and see what I'm doing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:50 a.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/earle/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/earle/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>David</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hanging out in the park and enjoying the weather. People watching, actually. Meeting friends later, and then getting some work done this afternoon.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably dinner. We know we're together for dinner, always. That's when we recap the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, I have an interview. So I'll be prepping for that all morning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:40 a.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/david/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/david/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Fran</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well mostly, I have been retired and I'm doing whatever I please today. As I do most every day. I'm going to go up to a friend's. Right now I'm sitting in the park reading my paper. I do that every morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is my backyard. I live two blocks away, over on Waverly and I love living in New York. I love it. I don't know why anybody would want to live anywhere else. Well, that's a little extreme. This is like my backyard. I like coming over here in the morning, I'm too old to enjoy the afternoon and evening nonsense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'd have to say, probably morning. Just because I'm an early person. I didn't like to get up and go to work, but I like to get up in the morning. I was a runner for a long time, and ran in the mornings. When my running was over, the best part of my day was over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's odd, most of my friends that are retired think I'm nuts. &quot;Why don't you sleep late?&quot; Well, sleeping late has never been something I want to do. So yeah, that's the favorite part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gee, I haven't thought that far ahead. I'm going away on Saturday, so I'm taking care of some things for that. I'm going up to Maine for a few days. Some shopping, seeing a friend, nothing very dramatic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>8:35 a.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/fran/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/fran/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Reuben</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I woke up early, so I'm going to skate for a while, then go to work. And then probably meet up with some friends afterwards, kick back a little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably the morning. I'm an early riser, I just wake up and I'm ready to go. I get out before a lot of my friends do. I get a lot more time skating, which is nice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I have work, so similar to today. Until I get off for a few days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:00 a.m. on Wednesday, August 14</pubDate>
				<link>/with/reuben/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/reuben/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Michelle</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, this morning I am sitting. I am sitting in the sun at the park. It's a perfect morning for it. It's not hot, it's not humid. It's just a lovely way to start the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you do this often?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As much as we can, yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Couple times a week? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It kind of depends. Once it starts getting warm, then it's not a good place for it. What I'll do on some mornings is, where I live it's a corner and the cross breeze is coming from two directions. So I'll just take, well not this chair, but a regular lawn chair and sit by the corner, by the apartment building, get the cross breeze, do that for an hour. Usually I read my newspaper. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;So you're in a bigger apartment building?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;So you can't just sit out on the stoop or anything. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, I don't have a stoop anymore. And I don't have a terrace, I would love a terrace. It's on the list of things I'd love to have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And how long have you lived around here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don't live in the heart of Bay Ridge, I'm sort of on the border. But basically, I've lived here for 45 years. My grandparents lived a block from where I live now. All my life, basically. I actually grew up in Bensonhurst, on 14th avenue, right across the street from the golf course. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And who do you live with now? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My sister. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And what time did you wake up this morning? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;6 o'clock. In the winter I sleep later and go to bed late. Go out when it's warmer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I do like the early morning. I like the quiet of the early morning. When you can open the windows and listen to the birds. And then, again I like late nights. It's quiet. I like the quiet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow it's supposed to rain, and I have a doctors appointment at 3 o'clock. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:00 a.m. on Wednesday, July 31</pubDate>
				<link>/with/michelle/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/michelle/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Juan</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm just getting a morning workout here. Pretty much, just shoot hoops in the morning. That's how I start my day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Every day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, I try to at least. Three times a week, at least. I've been trying to get back in shape, so I figured this would be the best way to start. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you live around here? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I actually live in Staten Island. But I work here and I have a lot of friends here. I usually come to Brooklyn a lot. I'm actually going to meet up with some friends after, so I figured I'd shoot here first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you guys going to do today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today we're going to head over to a friend's house to have a little barbecue. Just have some people over, hang out and enjoy the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up this morning?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I woke up around 6:30. Ate a little something, took a shower then headed out here. I've been here for about 30 minutes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Who do you live with?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now I live with my parents and my brother. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, I don't know if I'll be able to shoot hoops in the morning, but tomorrow I'll be working. So I won't be able to play hoops in the morning. But I'll see if I can get some sort of workout in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And what do you do for work? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work as a clerk in a hospital. I work evening shifts, so I work from 3pm until late at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably the morning. I'm a morning person. I feel like if you have a good start to the day, then the rest of the day should go pretty well. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:15 a.m. on Wednesday, July 31</pubDate>
				<link>/with/juan/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/juan/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Sophie</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well I went to try the bakery, Kayser. It's just around there. It's a French guy and they just started opening a new store and it's really, really good. I got bread and a raspberry financier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Is that all you have planned today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, it's very private. But actually, I took the day off because I'm pregnant and I have a big doctor appointment, so I just didn't want to rush from work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Congratulations! That's really exciting. And what time did you wake up today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like 7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;And what is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have an almost two year old son, so it's when I pick him up at daycare. He is all happy and I am happy too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back to work. It's not so fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:30 a.m. on Wednesday, July 24</pubDate>
				<link>/with/sophie/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/sophie/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Libby</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm shooting a student film, but the actor hasn't shown up yet. So these are some of the guys on the project. The director goes to New York Film Academy and he's waiting for the actor, who's over an hour late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn't usually happen. He's probably panicking more than me though. I'm just sitting here waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;How did you get over here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The F to the R, we met at Union Square and then walked up here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably evening. Usually because I'm done with work. I just like the light, and it cools off in the summer. It's nicer then. Early morning is nice too. I like the less hot parts of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I'm off, so I don't know, we'll see. I don't have to work. I've been doing some time lapse photography with flowers. So I have one flower that will hopefully will open. I did it yesterday, and I had it in the air conditioned living room and it didn't open. The kitchen is near the highway so it shakes. And it had leaves, so I'm going to cut the leaves off so they won't move as much. And I need the sun and the warmth. There's no air conditioning in the kitchen so I think it will open up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;So it's that fast that you can do this in one day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well it depends on the flower. I tried a flower outside in my garden from 6:30 to 9:30, but my camera starting overheating and it barely moved. I picked this dahlia and it's just really slow to open. Some I think will open. We'll see, I just started. This is my second flower. Hopefully I'll get some good stuff. I'm getting that flicker problem. Have you done time lapse before?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Not really. Is it shaking?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's not that it's shaking, it's the light changing. It reads like a flicker. I did one minute intervals yesterday, for about 7 or 8 hours. I kept it on the same exposure. The first time I did it — I just started doing these and if you change the shutter, I was changing to shutter to change exposure which was a big mistake. That was the first time I did it though. And I didn't do any research, it was kind of stupid. I just read how to use the intervalometer. But anyway, yesterday everything was consistent. I think the intervals are too long though so it fluctuates and it reads like a flicker. But it looked kind of cool. Even though nothing moved, the flower kind of breathed and went up and came back down. So yeah, I'm going to do that tomorrow. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:10 a.m. on Wednesday, July 24</pubDate>
				<link>/with/libby/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/libby/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Chris</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just hanging out here for a couple of minutes. I start work at 10 on 27th street So I biked down this morning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What do you do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm an acupuncturist. I've been doing it for seven years. I broke my back when I was 21 and that was the only thing that helped. I didn't end up getting surgery, but that was the only thing that was able to get the pain to go away. I was going to be a doctor before that, but after acupuncture worked, I was like &quot;fuck this shit, this is cool, I gotta learn how to do acupuncture so I can help people.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;So it was that effective that you went and did it yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yeah. Well, a lot of times in medicine, they're like, &quot;hey, let's see.&quot; It's someone listening to your problems, if something works even a little bit, it's a huge progress in the right direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you enjoy it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love it. It's a lot of work sometimes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I've been around Chelsea for the whole time. I've been in the office I'm at for four years now. But I'm moving in a couple of weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up this morning?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;6am&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you live by yourself?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I live with my fiancée.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What's your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the morning. And then the 15 minutes before I go to sleep. It's peaceful. In the morning I get to set up the intention of how the whole day is going to go and what I want to create. And at night it's nice to reflect on it and see what worked and what didn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, I have another office up in Westchester so I'll wake up early and drive up there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;You're not biking up there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, but one of these days I'm going to. It's only like 26 miles and there's a path. I'm in Mount Kisco so you can take the bike path all the way up the Saw Mill. They just don't have a shower up there, so it's been way to hot to just show up and start talking to people all sweaty. There's been days that have been bad. The A/C broke a couple weeks ago and I'm like blotting myself off with paper towels. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>9:20 a.m. on Wednesday, July 24</pubDate>
				<link>/with/chris/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/chris/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Robert</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m on my lunch break right now. I work in this building over here. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you enjoy it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What’s your favorite part of the day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five minutes before 4pm. Work ends and I get to go home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same exact thing. It’s like that movie, Groundhog Day, everything is the same, every day. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:55 p.m. on Wednesday, July 17</pubDate>
				<link>/with/robert/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/robert/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Richard</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm waiting for my wife who has a 12:30 appointment in this building over there. Then we're going to go home we’ll cook some dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh man, I woke up at 5:30 this morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Is that when you leave for work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, that's when I head out of the house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Where do you live?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We live out by Coney Island. We took the subway here today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What is your favorite part of the day? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;12 noon. That’s when I go to prayer at the church over on Fulton. I like it. It keeps me focused and away from the shenanigans in the street.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>1:10 p.m. on Wednesday, July 17</pubDate>
				<link>/with/richard/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/richard/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Muhammad</title>
				<description>&lt;p class='question'&gt;What are you doing today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m working here. Selling hotdogs, waters, gatorades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;How long have you been doing this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 week. I’ve been in this country for 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;What time did you wake up this morning?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I woke up at 8am. Then I took the subway here. I clean my stand, wipe it down and then my boss brings it here. I’ve been here one week, my boss was on this corner for four years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class='question'&gt;Do you enjoy this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I enjoy having a job. In this country people are just lucky to have a job. So I’m happy that I have this. Before, when I didn’t have a job, my head was all over the place. But now I’m focused.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
				<pubDate>12:45 p.m. on Wednesday, July 17</pubDate>
				<link>/with/muhammad/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/with/muhammad/</guid>
			</item>
			
		
	</channel>
</rss>